Boss
What the hell
What are you doing
Zane
Look
Look at the frogs you raised
How could this happen
They were fine last night
Like hell they were
You said you were a college grad
You said you knew the tech
Now they're all dead
Every single one is dead
I don't care
You're paying the six million compensation
What was that
You want me to pay
In your dreams
How much did I even make
And you want millions from me
Screw you
You
I quit
Keep this month's pay
So long
Come
Let's have a toast
This drink
Is to celebrate us making money
Lewes
You've worked so hard lately
Dad, Mom, Cynthia
Without your support
I wouldn't have made it
From now on
I'll never let you
Be looked down on again
Good
My son has made it
In the village
We won't have to take
crap from anyone
Well done
You've made the Liu family proud
Let's eat
From now on
Our good life
Is just beginning
Eat up
Lewes
Eat more
You've been exhausted lately